

Ioannis Tsilikas

Web Developer

My Contact

🕍 j.tsilikas.j@gmail.com

+30 6944293195

Rotterdam, Netherlands

<u>tsilikasioannis.com</u>

Skills

Html

CSS/LESS

Angular

• TypeScript

JavaScript

Bootstrap

APIs/Ajax

Middleware

Laravel

PHP

Django

Web scraping

Education Background

2016-Present
 International Hellenic University
 Bachelor Degree of Computer Science
 Engineering

Languages

English
 Certificate of Proficiency in English (ECPE)

GreekNative Speaker

Interests

- Music, art and cinema
- Hiking

About Me

Specializing in front-end development while maintaining a solid grasp of the whole stack, I excel at bridging the gap between the different sides of development.

Prioritizing team needs is my philosophy when it comes to effectively reaching project goals.

Beyond coding, I have a longstanding passion for digital painting. This creative pursuit informs my approach to mastering new skills.

Professional Experience

Arx.NET S.A. | Front-End Web Developer 2023 - Present

- Develop features for web Applications
- Refactor systems to increase performance
- Debug applications for smart TV platforms
- Assist with onboarding peers

Angular, Git, Linux/Bash, Nginx, Postman,

Freelance Illustrator 2016 – 2022

- · Worked under deadlines to deliver illustrations
- Assimilated client feedback
- Pursued and maintained client relationships

Photoshop, Illustrator, Procreate

Personal Projects

Job Listing Engine | Web scrapper Used web scraping technologies to create a job listing search engine that combined results from multiple vendors.

Django, Beautiful soup, Apache

Conference Hall Booking System | Thesis My theses is on developing a booking system for the university's shared conference halls.

Angular, Laravel, PHP, mySQL

Art portfolio website | <u>ioatsi.com</u> Personal website to showcase my digital painting work.

Angular, Netlify

Indie Game Projects | Volunteer Worked on two indie game projects as a 2D asset and concept artist.

Unity, GoDot, Blender